Trevor Morris

Full-Stack Software Engineer

tremorrisdev@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/trevor-a-morris/ https://tremorris.dev (509) 768-4050 Spokane, WA

I am an ambitious and dedicated full-stack engineer with 3+ years of experience solving real-world problems in both highly-collaborative environments and while working independently. I am always striving to learn and improve my craft.

Work Experience

Full-Stack .NET Developer

Sep 2024 - Present

Trans-System Inc. | Cheney

- Led front-end design and assisted with back-end infrastructure for a realtime chat and analytics platform facilitating 50, 000 daily interactions.
- Refactored several CI/CD pipelines which reduced release timelines by 50%.
- Supported and mentored junior engineers to facilitate a smooth and fast onboarding process.
- Worked in a team-based environment, emphasizing strong collaboration among developers, designers, and stakeholders to deliver high-quality software solutions.
- Created optimizations to back-end API request validation that removed roughly 40% of maintenance overhead across our web APIs.

Junior .NET Developer

Jun 2022 - Sep 2024

Trans-System Inc. | Cheney, WA

- Developed a document scanning application for digitizing and indexing driver paperwork, eliminating manual paperwork processing and saving over \$300,000 annually in associated costs.
- Designed and implemented critical infrastructure in a managed Android environment, streamlining bug reporting, log collection, and accelerating iteration processes.
- Upgraded several outdated internal applications from ASP.NET Core MVC to ASP.NET Core 8 and VueJS 3.

Volunteer Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

SparkCentral | Spokane

Volunteered as part of a program called Kids Drop In and Code aiming to remove financial and educational barriers for the next generation of engineers.

Core Skills

Front-End: Vue, Nuxt, UI, TypeScript, JavaScript, Node, Bun, Android, Tauri, Blazor, Razor, React, TailwindCSS, HTML

Back-End: ASP.NET, C#, REST APIs, SQL, Java, Go, Golang, CUDA, Rust, C, Kotlin, MSTest, OpenGL, Systems Development, PostgreSQL, Database Management

Tools: Git, PowerShell, CI/CD, Docker, Gradle, Bash, Azure DevOps, Azure, SSRS, Agile Development

Education

Eastern Washington University

Sep 2018 - Jun 2022

Bachelor of Science Computer Science